嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
哇  穿这么帅  要去哪里啊
Wow, you look nice. What's the occasion?
摩妮卡和我要庆祝交往满十个月  我们在乔治法国餐厅订了位
Monica and I are celebrating our 10-month anniversary.Got reservations at Jean-George. Wow.
你们怎么进得去
How'd you get in? Oh.
打了几通电话  动用一些关系
Made a few calls, pulled some strings
如果我们都吃鸡  不叫甜点  就让我们11点半进去
and they agreed to seat us at 11:30 if we both had the chicken and didn't get desert.
嗨  钱德  凯特琳  新发型喔
Hi, Chandler. Hey, Caitlin.Somebody got a haircut.
我恨死了  活像八岁小男孩
Ugh. I hate it. I look like an 8-year-old boy.
如果真的是这样  那以前上体育课就会相当有趣了
If that was true, gym class would've been  a lot more interesting.
正好27美元  好  给你
It's, uh, $27 even. Oh, okay. Here you go.
嘿  你的鸡呢  在后头  被这鸭子气跑了
Where's the chicken? Oh, it's in the back. The duck pissed him off.
鸭子说先有蛋  才有鸡
He said that eggs came first.
谢了  下回见  好  再见
Ha, ha, thanks. I'll see you later. Okay. Bye.
你那样算是什么  什么
What the hell was that? What?
打情骂俏
The flirting.
你不是正要去  跟谁来着
Aren't you supposed to be going out with, hmm, let's see,
跟我妹妹约会吗
my sister?
我没在打情骂俏啊  那根本就是打情骂俏
I was not flirting. It was totally flirting!
"新发型喔"
"Somebody got a haircut "
好  第一件事  你模仿得太差
First of all, the impression? Uncanny.
第二  那不是打情骂俏  只是两个人闲话家常而已
And second, that wasn't flirting. That was just casual conversation between two people. That is all.
我听你在说
Oh! Yeah, right.
你要看打情骂俏吗  我示范给你看
You wanna see flirting? I'll show you flirting.
算了  不用了
I'm good. I'm okay.
老友记  第五季  第19集  调情逊手
Friends  S05E19  The One Where Ross Can't Flirt
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
我真替乔伊感到骄傲
I am so proud of Joey.
他竟然要演《法网游龙》  我知道
He's gonna be on Law and Order! I know.
可是你不觉得  叫《网法游龙》比较对吗
But don't you think it should be called Order and Law?
不对  得先有法律才能去网啊
No because first they arrest the guy and then they try him.
我话匣子一开可就没完了
Yeah. Don't get me started on that.
我没在打情骂俏啊  还在纪念日当天  丢脸
I was not flirting. And on your anniversary. For shame!
怎么了  钱德跟外送的辣妹打情骂俏
What's going on? Chandler was hitting on the hot delivery girl.
我才没有  拜托你也小声点
I was not. And oh, God! Shh!
很抱歉  但有就是有
I'm sorry, but you were.
而且就算有  谁要跟她搭讪  也应该是个单身的男人
Okay? And besides, if anyone should be hitting on her ..it's the guy who's single
也应该是个有搞头的人嘛
the guy that who-who-who can do something about it.
看来有人想钓彼萨外送妹了
Sounds like someone wants to be Mr. Pizza Delivery Girl.
这个嘛  原来是这样  你喜欢凯特琳
Well... Is that what this is about? You like Caitlin?
罗斯  我们分手都两年了  中间你还结过婚
Ha, ha, Ross, we broke up two years ago. You've been married since then.
我们各自约会应该没问题吧
I think it's okay that we see other people.
我前几天在彼萨店看到她
Well, I-I was watching her the other day at the pizza place.
她性感又风趣
And she was just so sexy and funny
还有小巧可爱的
and has the cutest little
三围就不用说了
Okay, y'know what? We don't need her measurements. Ha, ha.
嘿  三个都是意大利腊肠彼萨
Okay Pepperoni, pepperoni, pepperoni.
罗斯  我知道她人美你又爱她  但她是不是蠢了点
Ross, I know she's pretty and you love her, but is she stupid?
她忘了我点的素食披萨了
She forgot my vegetarian.
太完美了
This is perfect.
她一定会回来送你的素食彼萨
She'll have to come back here with your pizza.
到时候  我就展现出我罗斯的魅力
And when she does, I will turn on the charm "au" Ross.
我真高兴你不吃肉
Oh, I am so glad you don't eat meat. Ha, ha.
看吧  吃素对大家都好
See? Vegetarianism benefits everyone. Mm.
嘿  大家看看  是谁来了  还记得我祖母吗
Hey, everybody, look who's here! You remember my grandmother.
重要的夜晚  太酷了
Big night! Yeah, it's so cool.
乔伊参与《法网游龙》演出  你一定很骄傲吧
Joey on Law and Order. You must be very proud.
钱德  她完全听不懂英文
Chandler, she doesn't understand a word of English.
抱歉  我以为你是乔伊的另一个阿妈
Ha, ha, I thought you were Joey's other grandmother.
我还猛说英文
I've done it again.
她是我的头号影迷
Nonnie's my biggest fan.
家族里只有她一个  从头到尾都相信我
Yeah, She's the only one in the family who's always believed in me.
对  他是大明星  我的胖胖乔伊大明星
Big star. My big fat Joey star.
对  我出生是27磅  所以
Yeah, I weighed, like, 27 pounds when I was born.
纪念日快乐  十个月纪念日快乐
Hey. Happy anniversary. Happy anniversary, 10 months.
我刚才在淋浴的时候  想起我们在伦敦的第一晚
So umm, when I was in the shower I was thinking about our first night in London.
乔伊的祖母来了
Oh, uh, Joey's grandmother's right there.
会说英文的还是不会的那个
Is that the one that speaks English or the one that doesn't?
不会的那个
The one who doesn't.
那一夜你给我的爱还真是火热
That was some hot love you gave me. Ha-ha-ha.
我去准备下  嘿  不如戴我送你的耳环
I'll get ready. Hey, why don't you wear those earrings I gave you?
好主意   就是要留到特别场合  好啊
Oh, that's a great idea. I was saving them for something special. Okay.
你得回家去
You've got to go home.
但是我喜欢这里啊
But I like it here.
你得回家拿我借你的耳环  钱德要我今晚戴那副耳环
You gotta go home and get the earrings that you borrowed from me okay? Chandler wants me to wear them tonight.
好  应该是放在我皮包里
Okay, well I think that they're in my purse.
你去穿衣服  我去找  好
Why don't you go get dressed and I'll look for them. Okay.
瑞秋  我要拿回我借你的耳环
Ahem, Rach. Hi.I need those earrings you borrowed.
好  我  马上回来  好
Okay. Yeah, I'll be right back. Okay.
菲比  你会说意大利语
Wow, Pheebs, you speak Italian?
我猜是吧
I guess so.
来  谢谢你
Here you go. Thanks.
瑞秋  等等  另外一个呢
Wait, Rach! Where's the other one?\r}
你两个都要
Oh, what,you-you want both of them? Ha, ha.
瑞秋凯伦葛林  另一个耳环呢
Rachel Karen Green, where's the other earring?
好啦  你先别生气
Okay, okay. Look, just don't freak out,
好像不见了  还在公寓里  但一定是不见了
but I kind of lost it. Oh, I know it's in the apartment, but I definitely lost it.
那我要怎么跟摩妮卡说  她今晚就要戴
Well, what am I going to tell Monica? She wants to wear them tonight!
叫她戴自己的耳环  这就是她的耳环
Tell her to wear her own earrings. These are her earrings.
不  不会吧
Nooo! Nooooo!
你把摩妮卡的耳环借我   我不能借她的东西
You lent me Monica's earrings? I'm not allowed to borrow her stuff.
为什么  因为我都会弄丢的
Why not? Because I lose her stuff!
他两点之后离开
He, uh, left a little after 2.
看到那个盲人没
Okay, You see that blind guy right there?
我等一下会痛打他一顿
I'm gonna bash his head in later.
我的主戏就快来了  主戏就快来了
Oh, uh, my big scene's coming up. Uh, the big scene coming up.
如果你说〝吃葡萄不吐葡萄皮〞  她会不会比较懂
If you said, "Big lima bean bubbling up," Would she understand the difference?
瑞秋  你在干嘛
Rach, what are you doing?
我不敢看   太恐怖了
Oh, I just can't watch. It's too scary.
现在是卖尿布的广告
Huh. It's a diaper commercial.
你也知道我的   小孩啊   责任  吓死人
Oh, yeah, well, you know me. Babies, responsibilities，ahhh!!!
彼萨外送  我来开  我来拿
Pizza delivery. I'll get it! I will get that!
嗨  嗨
Hi. Hi.
一个素食彼萨
One uh, vegetarian pizza.
12块半
That's $12.15. Ah.
对了  如果这会让你好过些  我正好很喜欢八岁男孩
Uh, by the way, if it makes you feel any better, uh  I happen to like 8-year-old boys.
什么
What?
我是说  不  不  之前你说过
Oh, I mean  No, no, no. The, uhYour hair. Before. Your hair.
你的发型很像八岁男孩
You said you thought your hair looked like an 8-year-old boy's
我说我很喜欢
and I'm just saying I like it.
你的发型
The hair.
谢谢
Oh. Thanks.
你知道  我不是真的喜欢八岁男孩
You want to see, I don't actually like 8-year-old boys.
我在等着你找钱
All I'm looking for is the money.
拿去  别再帮我们送彼萨了
Here you go. Now, stop bringing us pizzas, you.
我都快哭了
I'm gonna try. Ha, ha. Okay.
不客气
You're welcome.
你就是不想看我得手  对吧
You couldn't let me have her, could you?
什么
What?
我真的很喜欢这个女孩  你干嘛要来凑热闹
This is a girl I really like and you had to swoop in there!
怎么了   钱德冲着外送辣妹打情骂俏
What's going on? Chandler was totally flirting with the hot delivery girl.
真是多谢你了
Thank you for that.
我没有打情骂俏
I was not flirting.
没关系   我不在意  无所谓
It's okay. I don't care. Ha, ha. It's fine.
什么  真的
Really? Really?
小事一桩  我动不动也是这样
It's no big deal. I do it all the time.
你动不动就跟人打情骂俏
So, uh  Ahem. You flirt with guys all the time?
是啊  那又不代表什么  你不是也不代表什么意义吗
Sure. It doesn't mean anything. Just like I know it doesn't mean anything with you.
对啊  但是有一点很不一样  你比我辣多了
But there's a big difference. Sorry, You are a lot hotter than I am.
这是真的
True story.
钱德  你真的介意
Ha, ha. Chandler, This actually bothers you?
对  我是介意  我想很多人都会介意
Yes, it does bother me! And I think it'd bother a lot of people.
瑞秋  你和罗斯在一起那时
When you were going out with Ross,
他跟别的女人打情骂俏  你会不会介意
did it bother you when he flirted with other women?
不会  他跟别的女人上床  我才会介意
Uh, no. No, it bothered me when he slept with other women.
真是多谢了
And thank you for that.
但其实我没啥好担心的  罗斯从来就不太会打情骂俏
But I never had anything to worry about.Ross was never very good at the flirting thing.
什么  什么
What ? What ? Ha, ha.
你在说什么  对你不就有效
What are you talking about? It worked with you.
你说的真是对极了
Oh! Y'know what? you're right.
我们认识  你对我打情骂俏  九年后你终于追到我了
Oh! We met, you flirted and then, bam, nine years later, you had me.
好  好  就这么办
All right. All right.You know what I'm gonna do?
我再来点个披萨  等凯特琳来的时候
I am gonna order another pizza. And when Caitlin gets here
我来让你们见识一下  我有多会打情骂俏
you-you--I will show how well I flirt.
我还能要到她的电话号码
Yeah! I will, I will get her phone number! Oh, well
不是彼萨店的电话啦
And not the one on the menu.
我找到了 谢天谢地  在哪里找到的
I found it. Oh, thank God! Where was it?
在你的梳妆台上
On your dresser.
那是原来的那一个
Okay, that is the one we already have. Oh.
我的主戏到了  就是现在
Okay, here's my big scene. My big scene's here.
有人在吗
Anybody home?
天啊  干嘛
Oh, my God. What?
大家继续笑
Okay, everybody just keep smiling.
我祖母发现一定会难过到死掉
It'll kill my grandmother if she finds out. Ha, ha.
怎么了   我那段被剪掉了
Oh, what is it? Uh, they cut me out of the show.
什么
What?
你确定
Are you sure?
或许现在才轮到你上
Maybe your scene's coming up.
不太可能  看到那个装尸体的袋子没
Not likely. Because you see that body bag right there?
有啊  里头装的是我
Yeah. I'm in it.
太糟糕了  你要怎么办
This is terrible, what are you going to do?
不知道
I don't know.
我的老祖母活着  就是为了看我演戏
This little, old lady lives for my career.
上回《我们的日子》不要我  她差点难过到死掉
When they dumped me off Days of Our Lives, she almost died.
那样很不妙
That's not good.
你没在笑  别用那种表情  笑啊  大家继续笑
You're not smiling. Not that face! Smile, everybody smile! Ha, ha.
乔伊  你怎么不实话实说   那又不能怪你
Joey，Why don't you just tell her what happened? It's not your fault.
如果我们继续这样说话  会不会吓到她
If we keep talking this way, aren't we gonna freak her out soon?
很快  马上就轮我上场了
Oh, uh, soon. I'm gonna be on soon.
那就是我
There I am!
不  山姆瓦特斯顿
No.Sam Waterston!
不  不对  那是我  是我
Oh, no, no. That's me. That's me!
不是  那是山姆瓦特斯顿
No. Sam Waterston.
《爱与罪》 《摩羯一号大行动》
Crime Misdemeanor, Capricorn One.
她听不懂 〝你好〞  却知道《摩羯一号大行动》
She doesn't know "hello," but she knows Capricorn One.
菲比  我要那副耳环  节目一演完我们就要出去了
Phoebe! I have to have those earrings, we're going to leave as soon as the show is over
可是我已经还你了啊
But I already gave them back to you.
不  没有啊
No, you didn't.
好  我已经没还给你  我就是这样说的啊
All right, I already didn't gave them back to you. That's what I said.
瑞秋  另一个耳环在哪里
Ahem. Rachel，Where's that other earring?
菲比  不在这里
It's not here, Pheebs. It's not here. Oh!
我昨晚有去钱德和乔伊那里
I went to Joey and Chandler's last night!
好  记得要检查钱德的珠宝盒
Okay! Make sure you check Chandler's jewelry box.
慢着  钱德有珠宝盒
Wait a minute, Chandler has a jewelry box?
好了  时间紧迫  你要我现在就跟你解释
Okay, we have like ten minutes. Do you want me to get into that now?!
嘿  菲比  那个素食彼萨  你吃得还习惯吗
Hey Pheebs! How's that uh, vegetarian pizza working out for ya?
你和那些蔬菜  还真是有两下子  是吧
You and those vegetables have a real thing going on, huh?
你干嘛怪里怪气的
Why are you being weird?
你喜不喜欢
Do you like it?
不喜欢  否则我就会问 〝你干嘛装可爱〞了
No. That would be, "Why are you being cute?"
好吧  我在练习打情骂俏
Okay. I'm working on my flirting.
原来如此  我没看出来
Oh! I did not get that.
摩妮卡  你喜欢看 《法网游龙》吗
So, uh, Monica,do you like the Law & Order?
喜欢  很好看
Yeah, it's good. Oh.
我今天发现到了新的你
See, I'm finding out all this stuff about you today,
好比你爱看《法网游龙》
like you like the Law & Order
还有你到处跟人打情骂俏
and that you flirted with every guy in the Tri-State area!
好  我来问个清楚  你可以打情骂俏  我却不行
Okay, let me get this straight. It's okay for you to flirt, but not for me?
真高兴我们把话说清楚了
Oh, I'm so glad we cleared that up.
抱歉  但你听我说  男女有些事是不一样的
Look, I'm sorry, but some things are different for men and women.
继续   教我一些男女的差别
Go on, teach me about men and women.
虽然我已经教过你很多了  不过
Okay. I've already taught you so much already, but whatever.
你跟男人打情骂俏的时候
See when you flirt with a guy
你觉得只是打情骂俏  没啥大不了的
you think, "I'm just flirting, no big deal."
但对方会觉得  他终于找到人上床了
But the guy thinking, "Finally! Somebody who wants to sleep with me."
不可能  这是真的
No way! It's true.
真可悲  这也是真的
Well, that's pathetic. Again, true.
男人都这样吗   醒着的男人都适用
This goes for all guys? All guys that are awake.
等我们上床睡觉后
Then we go to sleep.
世界另一边的男人起床  继续做一模一样的事
All guys from the other end of the world wake up and behave the exact same way.
好  又进广告了  我还是没跟她说
All right. It's another commercial and I still haven't told her.
乔伊  这是像最后一段广告  你只剩十分钟
Joey, This is like the last commercial. Look, You've got 10 minutes left.
我知道  你要我怎么办
I know! What am I gonna do? Oh!
不许你落跑  留她在这里
No! You are not gonna run out and leave her here.
对  好啦
Yeah, all right. Oh!
乔伊
Joey?
乔伊  马上回来
Uh, Joey's gonna be right back.
马上回来
Right back?
我们顺便来聊聊你吧
Meanwhile, let's-let's-let's talk about you.
你年纪大  个子小
So, you're old and small.
嘿  找到没
Hey. Did you find it?
耳环是没有  但我在沙发底下  找到我的太阳眼镜
The earring? No. But look, I found my sunglasses under the couch!
我从去年夏天找到现在
I've been looking for these since last summer.
那是我借你的太阳眼镜
Those are my sunglasses. You borrowed them from me.
好  别激动  还你就是了
Okay. Calm down. Here they are.
菲比
Phoebe.
我们要怎么办   我不知道
What do we do? I don't know. I don't know!
我们只好老实跟摩妮卡说了
We'll just have to tell Monica, that's all.
老天  她一定会杀了我
Oh, God! She's gonna kill me.
我可以跟她说是我弄掉的
I suppose I could tell her it's just all my fault.
那就太好了
Oh, that'd be great.
摩妮卡  我有话要跟你说
Mon, could I talk to you?
好  什么事
Yeah. What is it? Um
我弄丢了你一只耳环  对不起  我真的很抱歉
I lost one of your earrings. I'm sorry. I am so, so sorry.
好吧  都弄丢了还能怎样
All right, well, I mean, what can you do? If you lost it, you lost it.
我保证会赔你一副新的  我真的很愧疚
I'll replace it, I promise. I feel so terrible.
没关系  你又不是故意的  不是
That's fine. You didn't do it on purpose. No.
瞧你难过的  来
Look at you. Come here.
好点了没  有啊  你最棒了
You feel better? Ha, ha. Yeah. You're the best.
好  等一等
Okay, wait a minute.
等一等  我不能这样
Wait a minute, I can't do this.
听着  其实不是菲比弄丢的
Listen, honey, it's not Phoebe's fault.
她把你的耳环借我  是我弄丢的  我真的很抱歉
She lent me the earrings. I lost it. I'm so sorry, honey.
我也觉得好愧疚
I feel terrible too.
所以我才不借给你东西
That is exactly why I do not lend you stuff!
先是我的首饰  不是首饰  就是我的蓝色毛衣
Okay?! I mean, first it's my jewelry! And if it's not my jewelry, it's-it's my blue sweater!
不是蓝色毛衣  就是我的太阳眼镜
And if it's not my sweater, it's my sunglasses.
你的太阳眼镜  对
Your sunglasses? Yes.
对啊
Oh, right.
彼萨外送  我的
Pizza. Oh, mine! Mine! Mine!
好  要开始了
Okay, here goes.
准备见识见识一流的打情骂俏
Prepare yourselves for some class-A flirting.
等等
Okay, hold on.
我准备好了
Okay.
你犯不着这样
Honey, you have nothing to prove.
如果你真的喜欢这个女孩  我也不觉得打情骂俏是好方法
If you really like this girl, I don't think flirting is the right way
等着看就知道  好吧
You'll see.Okay.
她叫什么名字
Oh, what's her name?
凯特琳
Caitlin!
Caitlin.
嘿
Hey.
这样吃下去也不是办法
Oh, we can't keep eating like this. Ha, ha.
12块半
Heh. It's, uh, $12.50.
好
Okay, um
所以
So
你们做彼萨  是用烧木头的炉子吗
Do you make the pizzas in one of those, uh, wood-burning ovens?
不是  其实是瓦斯炉
No, actually, I think they're gas.
瓦斯炉
Gas? Wow, ha, ha.
真带劲
Intense.
如果连盖勒家的人都这样打情骂俏的话
If this is the way all the Gellers flirt,
我们就没有问题了
we don't have a problem.
嘿  你知道瓦斯的味道吗
Hey, uh You know that smell gas has?
知道
Yeah.
那是加进去的  什么
They put that in. What?
瓦斯其实是无色无味
The gas is odorless.
加上味道  是为了让人在瓦斯漏气时能闻得出来
But they add the smell so you know when there's a leak.
好吧
Well, okay.
很多气体都有味道
A lot of other gas smells.
救命喔
Oh, the humanity.
甲烷有味道
Methane smells
不好意思  我真的得走了
You know what? Um, actually, I really should go.
我还没付钱呢
Oh, but I haven't paid you yet.
没关系  你们点了那么多  这一个算我请客
Y'know what? That's okay. You guys have ordered so many that this one's on me.
我是不是跟她说到瓦斯的事
Was I talking to her about gas?
那根本就是主题
More so than anything else.
我觉得很有意思
I-I-I found it interesting.
我很遗憾 不用
I'm sorry. Look, no-no, Hey, hey.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
九年之后  她和我就能在一起了
In nine years, she and I will be right there! Ha, ha.
好  我去清掉这些彼萨盒
Okay. Well, I'm gonna clear out some of these boxes.
罗斯  怎么了
Ross? Yeah?
还有哪些气体会加味道
What else do they add smell to?
凯特琳  嗨
Caitlin! Caitlin! Hi.
嗨  我是瑞秋
Hi, I'm Rachel. Oh.
住楼上的  叫一堆披萨的那家
From upstairs, people with all the pizza.
喔  披萨有问题吗  不是  披萨很好吃
Oh, was there a problem? No. No. Every thing's--they're fine.Great pizza.
其实  是我朋友罗斯
But, actually, um, my friend Ross
他只要打情骂俏就会紧张
he just gets really nervous when he's flirting.
天啊  他是在打情骂俏   没错
Oh, my God! That was flirting?  Yeah.
我知道你的感觉
I know, I know.
不过一旦过了那个阶段
but uh just, I'm telling you,  once, once you get past that part,
那个让你想要去死的阶段
where it just feels like you wanna die
你会发现  其实他是个大好人
he's-he's really a good person.
开口闭口都是瓦斯的那个人
The guy with the gas? Yeah.
给你说  他真的很体贴也风趣
I'm-I'm telling you， he's really sweet and really funny
还有一副好心肠
and he's just, oh, got a good heart.
而且我觉得  他很喜欢你  真的吗
And besides, I think he really likes you. Really?
我们七个人  却叫了十个披萨  这还不够明显吗
Well,y'know, we have seven people and 10 pizzas. What do you think?
我想说乔伊很会吃
I just, I thought Joey was there.
你可以留到星期一  然后我会强制驱离
You've got till Monday. Then I move to dismiss.
嘿  罗斯
Hey, Ross?
我刚才在走廊遇到凯特琳
Um, I just ran into Caitlin in the hallway and-and
你打情骂俏的技巧  肯定比我想像中更高明
Uh, you must be getting better at this flirting stuff than I thought. Ha, ha.
什么意思
What do you mean?
虽然我搞不懂  但她要我转交她的电话给你
I don't get it but she wanted me to give you her phone number.
她自己给你的   是啊
And she just gave you this? Yeah!
瑞秋  谢了  但我不需要你帮忙
Rach, thanks. But I don't need you doing me any favors.
我没帮忙啊  是她觉得你很可爱
I-I-I didn't! I didn't. She thought you were cute.
这点我倒是相信
Well, that I can believe.
嘿
Hey,
还在演吗
is the show still on?.
快要演完了
Almost over, man
那是罗马教皇吗
Oh! Is that the Pope?
我干嘛跟过去看
Why am I looking?
阿妈  来了  我的主戏上场
Oh, Nonnie, here I am! This is my big scene.
快退后
All right, back off!
我有枪
I got a gun!
用起来可不会手软
I'm not afraid to use it.
喔  乔伊  没错  阿妈
Oh, Joey. That's right, Nonnie.
你起码也该换一件上衣
You couldn't have at least changed your shirt?
我要你在手提箱里  装满十万美元
Now, I want a suitcase filled with $100,000
装满十万美元的小钞
Filled with $100,000 in small bills.
若是我没拿到
And if I don't get  Shoo!
And if I don't get it
我就毙了这只鸭子
I'm gonna shoot this duck!
不能这样
Oh, no!
我要出去了
I'm coming out!
她会相信吗
And she's supposed to buy this?
乔伊  太棒了
Joey, bravo!
地面控制队呼叫总部
Ground control to Major Tom
倒数开始
Commencing countdown
动力
Engines
全开
On
这是下周的片段  下周的
That's, uh, scenes from next week's show. Next week.
我一定要等着看
I am definitely gonna watch that.
这一副呢  看起来一样吗
What about these? Do these look the same?
一模一样
Definitely.
不是分开来看  那就不一样了
Not as each other.Oh, then, no.
嘿  嗨  准备好了
Hey, you ready? Hi. Yeah.
你真美
You look amazing. Aw.
我是全世界最幸运的男人
I'm the luckiest man in the world.
你即将要更幸运了
Oh, you're about to get a little luckier. Mm-hm.
耳环让我看看  喔对  耳环
Let me see the earrings. Oh, right, the earrings.
好看极了
They look great.
你男友真是品味一流
Does your boyfriend have the best taste or what?
我男友的品味真的很棒
My boyfriend really does have great taste.
多谢你帮我选耳环
Thanks for picking out the earrings man.Hm-mmm.